Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Lawrence, Reba, Aug. 1929 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Drafts of William R. George's diary.
  - Miller, Gerrit Smith; Strain, John D.; Kirkland, J.B., Sept. - Oct.1929 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    George Junior Republic legal case.
  - Holton, W.B., Nov. 1929 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Woollcott, Alexander; Welling, Richard, Dec. 1929 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Osborne, Harry V., Dec. 1929 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - "Daddy George's New Project"; Unsworth, Mary, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Christiancy, George A.C.; Cummings, Kate; Unsworth, Mary, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Cummings, Kate; Bartol, Leah; Guthrie, Donald G., Apr. - Dec.1929 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    Untitled article by William R. George concerning the principles of a Junior Republic.
  - Book drafts by William R. George, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Kirkland, J.B.; Faryolo, Vito; Forbes, W. Cameron; Levin, Leonard S., Jan. 1920 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Kirkland, J.B.; Welling, Richard; Smith, Jacob G.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Large, Harold; Strain, John D.; LeRoy, Harris G., Feb. - Mar.1930 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Strain, John G.; Forbes, Alexander; Kirkland, J.B.; McGraw, Ivan C.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Apr. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    George Junior Republic bonds.
  - Dapping, William O., May 1930 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Christiancy, George A.C.; London, Jack; Beach, William G.; Dapping, William O., Jun. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Edith George and Malcolm J. Freeborn wedding, Jul. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Fleming, Grace Cornell, Aug. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Schoonmaker, Hubert, Sept. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Agenda of helpers' meeting; New York Urban League.
  - LaMarche, George, Oct. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Smith, Jacob G.; Hotchkiss, Irene, Nov. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    League for the Promotion of Civic and Economic Responsibilities.
  - Addison, William Marlborough, Dec. 1930 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Letter from William R. George to the Executive Committee of the George Junior Republic Association; Constitution and By-laws of the National Association of Junior Republics.
  - Autobiographical statement of William R. George; Untitled article by William R. George concerning religion at George Junior Republic, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - "History in Brief of Things from the Time of Founding the Junior Republic to the Years 1930 or 1931" dictated by William R. George, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Autobiographical statement and untitled writings by William R. George, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Untitled writing by William R. George, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - "History of Self-Government.", 1930 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Draft concerning the Phalanx; "The George Junior Republic and Ten Sociological Projects that it Suggests.", Mar. - Dec.1930 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Smith, Jacob G., Jan. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Agenda for Executive Committee meeting; Transcript of radio address by William R. George. (Annotations.)
  - Merle-Smith, Kate Van Santvoord; Henry, Lillian, Feb. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Merle-Smith, Kate Van Santvoord, Mar. - Apr.1921 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Town Hall Club, May 1931 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Levin, Leonard S.; Franklin, Ruford; Baldwin, Summerfield; Shoemaker, Elizabeth T., Jun. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Insurance proxies.
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Fowler, Margaret B., Jul. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Hotchkiss, Willard E., Aug. - Sep.1931 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    New York Urban League.
  - "Revelations of a Social Laboratory on the Negro Social Doctor." (Annotations.), Oct. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - "The Revelation of a Social Laboratory.", Oct. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Hurley, John W.; Strain, Josephine; Offer, George E., Oct. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    National Child Welfare Association. (Annotations.)
  - Hubert, James H.; George, Orra K.; Holden, Arthur C.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Longan, Lou-Eva; Stoddart, Bessie D., Nov. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Guthrie, Donald; McAllister, Peter F.; Hamilton, R.L., Nov. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    Diet and regime pertaining to illness of William R. George.
  - McReynolds, M.F.; Osborne, Charles D.; McAllister, Peter F.; Freeborn, Malcolm J., Dec. 1931 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    Phalanx.
  - Untitled article by William R. George concerning George Junior Republic; "The Ten Projects"; Phalanx, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Woollcott, Alexander, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Plan of Activities for the Phalanx; Constitution of the Phalanx; List of endorsements concerning George Junior Republic by several well-known figures.
  - List of Phalanx members; Untitled article by William R. George concerning George Junior Republic, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Typescript of a talk by William R. George, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Draft of article for Encyclopedia Britannica; Phalanx, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Levin, Milton, Jan. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    United States Society.
  - Searles, Frank A.; LeRoy, Harris G., Feb. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Forbes, Alexander, Feb. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Lusk, Clayton R.; Smith, Jacob G., Mar. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Hughes, Charles E.; Jackson, Lorna Cooper, Mar. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    National Institute of Social Sciences; Autobiographical note by William R. George.
  - Perottino, Terziana; Eaker, Arthur T.; Stoddart, Evelyn L.; Burkholder, Horace C.; Freeborn, Edith G., Apr. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Kashmer, Anne, Jan. - Apr.1932 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Lusk, Clayton R., May 1932 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    National Institute of Social Sciences.
  - Lusk, Clayton R.; Guthrie, Donald; Levin, Leonard S.; Christiancy, George A.C., May 1932 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Rodier, Roscoe; Freeborn, Edith G.; Garimaldi, Edward, Jun. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    George Junior Republic Alumni Association; Phalanx.
  - Morter, Floyd E.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Welling, Richard, Jun. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Phalanx; National Institute of Social Sciences.
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Osborne, Charles D.; Osborne, Charles D.; Martin, Darwin S., Jul. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Urquhart, Donald T., Jul. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    George Junior Republic Alumni Association; National Institute of Social Sciences.
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Martin, Darwin D.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Dapping, William O.; Fox, William L., Aug. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Urquhart, Donald T. (Annotations.), Sept. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Langsam, Julia S.; Kinane, John J., Sept. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Untitled autobiographical chapter by William R. George, Jan. - Aug.1932 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Draft of a chapter by William R. George concerning Phalanx and the George Junior Republic, Sept. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Hahn, Rosina; Kane, Edward; Cummings, Kate; Tompkins, Elmer E.; Daly, Mark A., Oct. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Kinane, John J., Oct. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Levy, Aaron; Hay, Woodhull; Freeborn, Edith G.; Crinnion, Edward T., Nov. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Proposed Junior Municipality in Syracuse, N.Y.
  - Urquhart, Donald T.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Forbes, Alexander, Nov. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Letters to Curtis Reese and others discussing alumni and George family.
  - Chapter drafts by William R. George, Oct. - Nov.1932 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Stebbins, Agnes N.; Cummings, Kate, Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    Proposed Warner Brothers Pictures, Inc. movie called "Junior Republic."
  - Witmark, Isador; Forbes, Alexander; Smith, Jacob G.; Freeborn, Edith G.; King, Ruth, Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Letter from William R. George to Warner Brothers Pictures, Inc.
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Guthrie, Donald; Hurley, John W., Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    "The Social Doctor and the Social Sanitarium." (Annotations.)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; London, Jack, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    Letter to ex-citizens from Edith G. Freeborn; Lists of alumni and Phalanx members; Untitled articles by William R. George concerning the Phalanx and social service; Phalanx.
  - Witmark, Isador; Freeborn, Edith G., Dec. 1932 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Warner Brothers Pictures, Inc.; Untitled articles by William R. George concerning Syracuse, N.Y. as a social laboratory.
  - Cummings, Kate; Rodier, Roscoe; Urquhart, Donald T.; Thomas, Lowell, Jan. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    "The Adult Minor."
  - Edison, Charles, Jan. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Welling, Richard, Jan. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    National Self Government Committee, Inc.; Excerpt from diary of William R. George.
  - Cummings, Kate; Hodge, Gertrude; Lusk, Clayton R., Jan. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Kashmer, Anne; Guthrie, Donald; King. Ruth, Feb. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    George Junior Republic Bar Examination; "The Men of Tomorrow are the Men of Today"; Untitled article by William R. George concerning the 1914 events at the George Junior Republic.
  - LeRoy, Harris G.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; King, Ruth; Miller, Hervey E.; Dixey, Thomas, Feb. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Cornell Liberal Club.
  - Kinane, John J., Feb. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    "The Junior Governmental Plan" by Malcolm J. Freeborn.
  - Richards, Harry E.; Stoddart, Bessie D., Mar. 1933 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    Military Training Camps Association; "The Story of the Massachusetts Cottage" by William R. George.
  - Hadley, Edwin M., Apr. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    The Paul Reveres; Child Labor Amendment; Untitled article by William R. George concerning Bishop Henry C. Potter and worship services at the George Junior Republic.
  - Richards, Harry E.; Cummings, Kate; Kinane, John J., Apr. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    "Suggestions for Junior Republic at Freeville, N.Y."; The Paul Reveres; "Eleven Projects of the League."
  - Carter, William; Smith, Jacob G.; Kinane, John, J.; Guthrie, Donald; Forbes, Alexander; Freeborn, Edith G., May 1933 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Committee on American Education; Friends of the Soviet Union; "Plans for a Large Scale Method of Democratic Training for Youth" by Malcolm J. Freeborn.
  - Cummings, Kate; Kinane, John J., Jun. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Junior Crusaders; The Paul Reveres.
  - Kinane, John J.; Freeborn, Edith G.; LeRoy, Harris G., Jun. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Untitled article by William R. George concerning the crisis of policy at the George Junior Republic
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Jan. - May1933 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Warner Brothers Pictures, Inc.; "An Explanation" by William R. George concerning the Phalanx and other organizations; "The Ten Projects"; Letter from William R. George to the Freeborns about the Phalanx and relevant causes; Phalanx
  - Untitled article by William R. George; "What is a Junior Republic?", Jun. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Vredenburg, Edward; Hadley, Edwin M.; Lincoln, Alexander; Van Tassel, Dorothy; Balch, Katherine T., Jul. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    The Paul Reveres; Sentinels of the Republic!
  - Dapping, William O.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Osborne, Lithgow; McGraw, Ivan C., Aug. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Letter by William R. George to New York Times; League of Adult Minors.
  - Crinnion, Edward T.; Freestone, Fred, Aug. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Kirkland, J.B.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Broadhurst, Iva, Sept. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    "Change in Junior Republic" by William R. George; League of Adult Minors.
  - Kinane, John J.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Armstrong, Clarence, Sept. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Letter to Phalanx members; Child Labor Amendment; League of Adult Minors.
  - Armstrong, Clarence; Kinane, John J.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Sabo, Clara, Sept. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    "Youth Stands His Ground" by John J. Kinane; The Paul Reveres; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Crinnion, Edward T.; Cummings, Kate; Balch, Katherine T.; Sabo, Clara; Kinane, John J., Oct. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Sentinels of the Republic !; Untitled article by William R. George concerning adult minors; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Rodier, Roscoe; Crinnion, Edward T.; Balch, Katherine T.; Kinane, John J.; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Barnum, Jerome D., Oct. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    Phalanx; Child Labor Amendment; Junior Municipality.
  - Barnum, Jerome D.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Kinane, John J.; Freeborn, Edith G., Oct. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Child Labor Amendment
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Balch, Katherine T.; Barnum, Jerome D.; Freeborn, Malcolm J., Nov. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    Child Labor Amendment; Letter from Malcolm J. Freeborn to William R. George concerning Donald Urquhart's administration of the George Junior Republic.
  - Barnum, Jerome D.; Kilbreth, Mary G., Nov. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Barnum, Jerome D.; Kilbreth, Mary G; Buckley, Charles H.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Daly, Mark A., Dec. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Kinane, John J.; Peck, Grace B.; Butler, Nicholas Murray; Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Crinnion, Edward T., Dec. 1933 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    League of Women Voters; Untitled article by William R. George on the Child Labor Amendment.
  - Oliver, Adele Colson, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    "An American Youth Republic" by Erich Vowes; Constitution of the League of Adult Minors; Untitled article by William R. George detailing history of his objection to the Child Labor Amendment.
  - League of Adult Minors; Untitled article by William R. George; Rules and penalties at the George Junior Republic; Child Labor Amendment, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Kinane, John J., 1933 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Van Tassel, Dorothy, Jul. - Sep.1933 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    "Change in Junior Republic"; Address by Nicholas Murray Butler.
  - Kinane, John J.; Van Tassel, Dorothy, Oct. - Dec.1933 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    Untitled articles by William R. George concerning adult minors and the George Junior Republic.
  - Kinane, John J.; McClellan, William F.; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Butler, Nicholas Murray; Sabo, Clara; Broadhurst, Iva, Jan. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Crinnion, Edward T.; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Andrews, Lenore; Hodge, Gertrude, Jan. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Kinane, John J.; Talk by William R. George on the Child Labor Amendment, Jan. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Crinnion, Edward T.; Barnum, Jerome D.; Guthrie, William D.; Rosenthal, Max, Feb. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    Child Labor Amendment; National Committee for the Protection of Child, Family, School and Church.
  - Miller, Gerrit Smith; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Edmunds, Sterling E., Feb. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    "A Civic Training Program for the Adult Minor."
  - Sabo, Clara; Crinnion, Edward T.; Farrand, Livingston; Kinane, John J.; Hahn, Rosina, Feb. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    National Committee for the Protection of Child, Family, School and Church; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Farrand, Livingston; Barrett, Josephine; Guthrie, William D.; Burden, Henry; Fish, Hamilton; Stebbins, Agnes, Mar. 1924 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    Child Labor Amendment; Constitution of the League of Adult Minors.
  - Sampson, Hazel W.; Zalkan, Melvin C.; Albertson, Henry H.; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Stebbins, Agnes., Mar. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    Child Labor Amendment; George Junior Republic court case; Sentinels of the Republic! (Annotations.)
  - Dreyfus, Fred J.; Sabo, Clara; Stebbins, Agnes; Torbert, H.G.; Barnum, Jerome D.; Crinnion, Edward T., Mar. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Latorraca, Theresa; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Welling, Richard; Guthrie, William D.; Butler, Nicholas Murray; Crinnion, Edward T.; McCormick, John T.; Wilson, Albert H.; London, Jack, Apr. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    Child Labor Amendment; "To All Those Interested in Our Boys and Girls" by Charles V. Hoffman.
  - Sabo, Clara; Kinane, John J.; Sargent, Noel; Gerrish, Donald H.; Kilbreth, Mary G.; Rodier, Roscoe, Apr. 1934 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    Address by Edward T. Crinnion; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Kinane, John J.; Hoffman, Charles V.; Lowrie, Sarah D., May 1934 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Sargent, Noel; McCormick, John F.; Stone, J. Sumner; Edmunds, Stanley E., Jun. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    "Notes on Biography of William R. George"; Child Labor Amendment. (Annotations.)
  - Barnum, Jerome D.; Kinane, John J., Jun. 1924 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Welling, Richard; LeRoy, Harris G.; Rosenthal, Max; Sargent, Noel, Jul. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Untitled article by William R. George concerning Child Labor Amendment. (Annotations.)
  - Lusk, Clayton R.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Jung, Harry A.; Kinane, John J.; Sargent, Noel; McFarland, J. Horace, Aug. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    The Adult Minor Governmental Program; American Vigilant Intelligence Federation; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Sabo, Clara; Kinane, John J.; Stutz, Harry, Jan. - Jul.1934 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Draft by William R. George, Aug. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Sargent, Noel; Kinane, John J., Sept. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Curtice, Jesse P.; Kinane, John J.; Miller, Gerrit Smith, Oct. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - McFarland, J. Horace; Sabo, Clara, Nov. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - DeArmas, Nico; Hahn, Rosina; Freeborn, Edith G.; Reiman, Walter, Dec. 1934 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    The Paul Reveres.
  - Kinane, John J., 1934 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    American Youth Congress; Constitution of the League of Adult Minors; George Junior Republic court case; "The Community and Youth Problems" by Malcolm J. Freeborn; "What Is the Junior Municipality?"
  - "Adult-Minor Citizenship" by Malcolm J. Freeborn; Untitled article by William R. George, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Handwritten draft notes for books or articles by William R. George, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - McFarland, J. Horace; Smith, Jacob G., Sept. - Dec.1934 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Untitled article by William R. George, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Van Tassel, Dorothy; Broadhurst, Iva; Sabo, Clara, Jan. 1925 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Sabo, Clara; Miller, Hervey E; Tobin, Charles J.; Guthrie, William D; Edmunds, Stanley E., Jan. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Sargent, Noel; Torbert, H.G.; Freeborn, Edith G., Feb. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    "To the Executive Committee of the George Junior Republic Association, Inc." and "Participation in Government by the Adult Minor" by Malcolm J. Freeborn; Child Labor Amendment.
  - Urquhart, Donald T.; McFarland, J. Horace, Feb. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - London, Jack; LeRoy, Harris G.; Osborne, Charles D.; Osborne, Thomas Mott; Kauffman, Robert B.; Freeborn, Malcolm J., Mar. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Latorraca, Theresa; Forbes, Alexander; Urquhart, Donald T., Apr. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Van Tassel, Dorothy, May 1935 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Jacob G., May 1935 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Freeborn, Edith G. (Annotations.), Jun. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Dayton, George M.; Welling, Richard, Jun. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    Letter from William R. George to the Freeborns.
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Forbes, Alexander; Barnum, Jerome D.; Rexford, Frank A; Reed, Daniel A.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Welling, Richard, Jul. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    Letter from William R. George to the Freeborns; California George Junior Republic.
  - Kirkland, J.B.; Sabo, Clara; Rockwell, Vera C., Jul. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    William R. George's resignation from the Board of Trustees of the George Junior Republic.
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Crinnion, Edward T., Jul. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    American Liberty League.
  - Benjamin, Arthur; Sargent, Noel; Rockwell, Vera C.; Guthrie, Donald, Jul. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Benjamin, Arthur; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Kinane, John J.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Forbes, Alexander, Aug. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Smith, Jacob G.; McAllister, Peter F., Aug. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    "A Righteous Cause Founded on Justice Must Live"; Untitled article by William R. George about George Junior Republic.
  - Kinane, John J., Aug. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    Untitled writings by William R. George.
  - Rexford, Frank A., Feb. - Jun.1935 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Forbes, Alexander, Jul. 1935 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Rockwell, Vera C., Sept. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Kinane, John J.; Rockwell, Vera C., Sept. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Urquhart, Donald T., Oct. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    "Autobiography" by William R. George.
  - Forbes, Alexander; Coyle, Philip J.; Kinane, John J.; Rockwell, Vera C., Oct. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Weston, Emma, Nov. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; McCormick, John F., Nov. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Forbes, Alexander; McCormick, John F.; Sabo, Clara, Dec. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Notes by Malcolm J. Freeborn concerning William R. George and property sale at George Junior Republic.
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Offer, George E., Dec. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Map of George family homestead.
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Forbes, Alexander, Aug. - Nov.1935 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Untitled writings by William R. George, Dec. 1935 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - "My Life" and autobiographical notes by William R. George, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - "The Adult Minor," drafts and notes, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - McCormick, John F.; Kinane, John J.; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; McAllister, Peter F.; Dicker, Martin, Jan. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Dicker, Martin; Rockwell, Vera C., Jan. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Crinnion, Edward T.; Dicker, Martin, Feb. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - King, Edward M.; Smith, Jacob G.; Dicker, Martin, Feb. 1926 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - McAllister, Peter F.; Rockwell, Vera C., Feb. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Legal agreement between the George Junior Republic Association and William R. and Esther B. George.
  - Latorraca, Theresa; Rockwell, Vera C.; Morse, Elizabeth L.; Welling, Richard, Mar. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Rockwell, Vera C., Mar. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    League of Adult Minors; "Day by Day"; "Concerning Child Labor Amendment."
  - Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Rockwell, Vera C., Mar. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    "The Proposed Child Labor Amendment" by William R. George.
  - Crinnion, Edward T.; Rockwell, Vera C., Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    "A Republic," and "The Social Order" by William R. George. (Annotations.)
  - Robbins, Jack. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Rockwell, Vera C.; Smith, Jacob G.; Burns, John C.; Freeborn, Edith G. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Sabo, Clara; Latorraca, Theresa. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Hurley, John W.; Sargent, Noel; Welling, Richard; Miller, Gerrit Smith; LeRoy, Betty. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Kirkland, J.B.; Broadhurst, Iva; Donlon, Mary H.; Strain, John D., Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    Sympathy correspondence; Ithaca Journal obituary. (Annotations.)
  - Sympathy correspondence. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Franklin, Ruford, Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Sympathy correspondence. (Annotations.)
  - Forbes, Alexander, Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Sabo, Clara; Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Guthrie, Donald, Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Untitled article by William R. George; Sympathy correspondence. (Annotations.)
  - Rodier, Roscoe, Feb. - Mar.1936 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    Autobiographical notes by William R. George.
  - Sympathy telegrams. (Annotations.), Apr. 1936 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Kirkland, J.B., May 1936 (Box 37, Folder 1)